<!-- Plugin Configuration File: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-configuration-file.html -->
<idea-plugin>
    <!-- Unique identifier of the plugin. It should be FQN, cannot be changed between the plugin versions. -->
    <id>com.jellybebra.ContextCombiner</id>

    <!-- Public plugin name should be written in Title Case. -->
    <name>Context Combiner</name>

    <resource-bundle>messages.MyMessageBundle</resource-bundle>

    <!-- A displayed Vendor name or Organization ID displayed on the Plugins Page. -->
    <vendor url="https://github.com/jellybebra">JellyBebra</vendor>

    <!-- Description of the plugin displayed on the Plugin Page and IDE Plugin Manager. -->
    <description><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Boost your AI coding workflow with ContextCombiner!</b></p>
        <p>
            ContextCombiner is a productivity tool designed to help developers quickly gather code context for Large Language Models (LLMs) like ChatGPT, Claude, DeepSeek, or GitHub Copilot.
        </p>
        <p>Instead of manually copying and pasting multiple files, simply right-click a folder and export everything in a structured format.</p>

        <p><b>Key Features:</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li>🚀 <b>Easy Context Gathering:</b> Right-click any file or folder in the Project View to start.</li>
            <li>🌲 <b>Interactive Selection:</b> Select or deselect specific files using a convenient tree view with checkboxes.</li>
            <li>📝 <b>LLM-Friendly Format:</b> content is automatically wrapped in Markdown code blocks (<code>```</code>) with clear file headers (<code>### path/to/file</code>), making it easy for AI to parse.</li>
            <li>🛡️ <b>Smart Filtering:</b> Automatically ignores:
                <ul>
                    <li>Hidden files (starting with dot)</li>
                    <li>Binary files (images, compiled archives)</li>
                    <li>Files ignored by Git (respects <code>.gitignore</code> via IDE VCS integration)</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>

        <p><b>How to use:</b></p>
        <ol>
            <li>Right-click a folder or file in the <b>Project View</b>.</li>
            <li>Select <b>"Copy Context for LLM..."</b>.</li>
            <li>Review the file list in the dialog and uncheck any unnecessary files.</li>
            <li>Click <b>OK</b> — the formatted context is now in your clipboard, ready to paste!</li>
        </ol>
    ]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <notificationGroup
                id="ContextCombiner.Notifications"
                displayType="BALLOON"
                key="notification.group.context.combiner"/>
    </extensions>

    <!-- Product and plugin compatibility requirements. -->
    <actions>
        <action id="com.jellybebra.contextcombiner.ContextCombinerAction"
                class="com.jellybebra.contextcombiner.ContextCombinerAction"
                text="Copy Context for LLM..."
                description="Select files and copy their content to clipboard"
                icon="/icons/magicStack.svg">
            >

            <!-- Добавляем в контекстное меню дерева проекта (Project View) -->
            <add-to-group group-id="ProjectViewPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
        </action>
    </actions>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <p><b>1.0.2</b></p>
        <ul>
            <li>Added per-file size and estimated token count in the selection tree.</li>
            <li>Added a live selection summary with selected file count, total size, and approximate token usage.</li>
            <li>Added Expand all and Collapse all actions for faster navigation in large trees.</li>
            <li>Made the root item visible in the popup to provide better folder context.</li>
            <li>Changed hidden and Git-ignored file behavior: they are now shown in the tree but unchecked by default instead of being fully hidden.</li>
            <li>Added a notification after copying context to the clipboard, including the number of exported files.</li>
            <li>Registered a dedicated notification group and bumped the plugin version from 1.0.1 to 1.0.2.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

</idea-plugin>
